Indiana University President's Office records, 1937-1962 C213
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1937-1962
  - Walters, Basil, 1954 (Box 575)
  - Walters, Raymond, 1939-1959 (Box 575)
  - War, 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 575)
  - War, 1939-1962; (23 folders) (Box 576)
  - War Manpower Commission, 1942-1943 (Box 576)
  - War Service Opportunities, 1942-1943 (Box 576)
  - War Service Plan, 1942-1943 (Box 576)
  - War Training Program, 1942-1944; (5 folders) (Box 576)
  - War Time Conversion, 1943-1944 (Box 576)
  - War Training Program, 1942-1943; (4 folders) (Box 576)
  - E.S.M.W.T., 1943-1944 (Box 576)
  - War Training Program, 1943-1944 (Box 576)
  - War Training Program, 1943-1945; (12 folders) (Box 577)
  - AST Bulletin and Other Pub., 1944-1945 (Box 577)
  - WTP, 1944-1945 (Box 577)
  - U.S.-Armed Forces Institute, 1944-1945 (Box 577)
  - War Bonds, 1945-1946 (Box 577)
  - War Mobilization and Reconversion Act, 1946-1947 (Box 577)
  - WTP, 1945-1946; (5 folders) (Box 577)
  - E.S.M.W.T., 1945-1946 (Box 577)
  - U.S.-Armed Forces Institute, 1945-1946 (Box 577)
  - WTP, 1945-1946 (Box 577)
  - Warn, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 577)
  - Warren, Patrick Company, 1937-1938 (Box 577)
  - Warner, Archie, 1938-1939 (Box 577)
  - Was, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 577)
  - Waseda University, 1952-1957 (Box 577)
  - Washington Folder, 1939-1940 (Box 577)
  - Washington, George University, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 577)
  - Washington State College, 1939-1940 (Box 577)
  - Washington State College, 1940-1951; (12 folders) (Box 578)
  - Washington, University of, 1937-1945; (8 folders) (Box 578)
  - Washington Terrace Apartments (Box 578)
  - Wat, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 578)
  - Water Plant, 1937-1938 (Box 578)
  - Water Shortage, 1959 (Box 578)
  - Water Situation at Bloomington, 1939-1940 (Box 578)
  - Watkins, Oscar L., 1943-1944; (2 folders) (Box 578)
  - Watson, James Dewey (Box 578)
  - Watt, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 578)
  - We, 1937-1945; (9 folders) (Box 578)
  - We, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 579)
  - Wea, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 579)
  - Weatherwax, Prof. Paul, 1937-1957 (Box 579)
  - Weaver, W.W. Claim, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 579)
  - Web, 1946-1947 (Box 579)
  - Webs, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 579)
  - Wei, 1937-1950; (13 folders) (Box 579)
  - Wei, 1950-1962; (12 folders) (Box 580)
  - Weimer, Arthur M., 1937-1962; (26 folders) (Box 580)
  - Weir, James R., 1942-1943 (Box 580)
  - Weir, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 580)
  - Wel, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 580)
  - Wel, 1941-1962; (20 folders) (Box 581)
  - Welch, W. Bruce, 1945-1951 (Box 581)
  - Welli, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 581)
  - Wells, Agnes E., Dean of Women (Box 581)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 581)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 581)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 581)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 581)
  - Wells, Clifford, 1937-1938 (Box 581)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1936-1939; (12 folders) (Box 581)
  - Wells, Mr. and Mrs. Granville, 1938-1939 (Box 581)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1938-1940; (9 folders) (Box 581)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1939-1941; (7 folders) (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B--Madison, Indiana Rotary Club, 1940-1941 (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1940-1942; (16 folders) (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B--Books Library Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B--Madison, Indiana Rotary Club, 1941-1942 (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1941-1943; (12 folders) (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B--Books, Advertisements for, 1942-1943 (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1942-1944; (15 folders) (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B--Letters of Congratulation, 1943-1944 (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B--Correspondence with President's Office, 1943-1944 (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B--Applications, 1943-1944 (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1943-1945; (24 folders) (Box 582)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1944-1946; (30 folders) (Box 583)
  - Wells, Herman B--Commencement Luncheon, 1945-1946 (Box 583)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1945-1947; (28 folders) (Box 583)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1940-1948; (28 folders) (Box 584)
  - Wells, Herman B--Commencement Tea Reception, 1947-1948 (Box 584)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1947-1948 (Box 584)
  - Wells, Herman B--Indianapolis Symphony Buffet, 1947-1948 (Box 584)
  - Wells, Herman B--Eugene Pulliam Dinner, 1947 (Box 584)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1947-1949; (8 folders) (Box 584)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1948-1949; (20 folders) (Box 585)
  - Wells, Herman B--Indianapolis Symphony Buffet, 1948-1949 (Box 585)
  - Wells, Herman B--Commencement Tea Buffet, 1948-1949 (Box 585)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1948-1950; (22 folders) (Box 585)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1949-1950; (7 folders) (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B--Indianapolis Symphony Buffet, 1949-1950 (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1949-1950; (3 folders) (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B--U.S. State Department Mission to Germany, 1949-1950 (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1949-1951; (12 folders) (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B--Christmas Gifts Sent 1950-State Officials, 1950-1951 (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1950-1952; (23 folders) (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B--Christmas Gifts Sent 1951-State Officials, 1951-1952 (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1951-1952 (Box 586)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1951-1952; (8 folders) (Box 587)
  - Wells, Herman B--National Committee for a Free Europe, Inc., 1951-1954 (Box 587)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1951-1952; (3 folders) (Box 587)
  - Wells, Herman B--Little 500, 1951-1952 (Box 587)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1951-1952 (Box 587)
  - Wells, Herman B--Faculty Tea, October 4, 14 (Box 587)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1951-1954; (54 folders) (Box 587)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1953-1954; (7 folders) (Box 588)
  - Wells, Herman B--Real Estate, 1953-1955; (2 folders) (Box 588)
  - Wells, Herman B--Christmas Gifts Sent 1955-State Officials, 1955-1956 (Box 588)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1955-1956; (5 folders) (Box 588)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1955-1957; (25 folders) (Box 589)
  - Christmas Cards Ack'd by note, 1956 (Box 589)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1957-1959 (Box 590)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1958-1960; (42 folders) (Box 591)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1959-1961; (88 folders) (Box 592)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1960-1962; (36 folders) (Box 593)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1961-1962; (12 folders) (Box 594)
  - Wells, Herman B--Open House, 1961-1962 (Box 594)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1961-1962 (Box 594)
  - Wen, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 594)
  - Wer, 1947-1955; (7 folders) (Box 594)
  - Wert, Quentin, 1937-1938 (Box 594)
  - Wes, 1937-1950; (13 folders) (Box 594)
  - Wes, 1950-1962; (12 folders) (Box 595)
  - Wesley Foundation, 1939-1943; (4 folders) (Box 595)
  - West, Thomas M., 1942-1943 (Box 595)
  - West Point Competitive Examination, 1938-1948; (9 folders) (Box 595)
  - West Virginia University, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 595)
  - Weste, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 595)
  - Western State Normal School, 1938-1939 (Box 595)
  - Westwood Mills Christian Church, 1954-1955 (Box 595)
  - Wey, 1937-1954; (16 folders) (Box 595)
  - Wh, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 595)
  - Whaples, George, 1939-1961 (Box 595)
  - Whi, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 596)
  - Whit, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 596)
  - White, 1946-1954; (8 folders) (Box 596)
  - White, 1954-1955 (Box 597)
  - White, William Allen, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 597)
  - White House Conference on Education, 1955-1956; (2 folders) (Box 597)
  - Whiti, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 597)
  - Whitlock, Douglas, 1955-1959; (4 folders) (Box 597)
  - Who's Who in America, 1960 (Box 597)
  - Wi, 1937-1959; (22 folders) (Box 597)
  - Wi, 1959-1962; (3 folders) (Box 598)
  - Wie, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 598)
  - Wil, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 598)
  - Wilder, R.L., 1942-1943 (Box 599)
  - Wildermuth, Joe H., 1939-1940 (Box 599)
  - Wildermuth, Judge O.L., Board of Trustees (Box 599)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 599)
    - 1938-1939, (folder 1 of 2) (Box 599)
    - 1938-1939, (folder 2 of 2) (Box 599)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 599)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 599)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 599)
    - 1942-1943, (folder 1 of 2) (Box 599)
    - 1942-1943, (folder 2 of 2) (Box 599)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 599)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 599)
  - Wildermuth, Judge O.L., Gary, Indiana (Box 599)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 599)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 599)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 599)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 599)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 599)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 599)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 599)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 599)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 599)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 599)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 599)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 599)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 599)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 599)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 599)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 599)
    - 1958-1961 (Box 599)
  - Wilh, 1937-1941 (Box 599)
    - 1931-1938 (Box 599)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 599)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 599)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 599)
  - Wilkerson, Delphia, 1940-1941 (Box 599)
    (Consists solely of cross references)
  - Wilking Music Company (Box 599)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 599)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 599)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 599)
  - Will, 1937-1949 (Box 599)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 599)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 599)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 599)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 599)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 599)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 599)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 599)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 599)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 599)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 599)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 599)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 599)
  - Will, 1949-1962; (13 folders) (Box 600)
  - Will, Samuel F., 1947-1961 (Box 600)
  - Willbern, Glen D., 1938-1961 (Box 600)
  - Willbern, York Young, 1957-1962 (Box 600)
  - Willi, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 600)
  - Williams, 1941-1951; (7 folders) (Box 600)
  - Williams, 1951-1955; (4 folders) (Box 601)
  - Williams, Dean Elmer (Box 601)
  - Williams, Joseph E., 1960-1961 (Box 601)
  - Williams, Prof. K.P., 1937-1959; (10 folders) (Box 601)
  - Williamson, Jesse, 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 601)
  - Willis, Prof. Hugh E., 1937-1943 (Box 601)
    - 1937-1950 (Box 601)
    - 1951-1962 (Box 601)
  - Wilm, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 601)
  - Wils, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 601)
  - Wilson, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 601)
  - Wilson, Stuart, 1947-1962 (Box 601)
  - Wilt, Frederick, 1942-1943 (Box 601)
  - Wim, 1941-1962; (20 folders) (Box 601)
  - Win, 1937-1950; (7 folders) (Box 601)
  - Win, 1950-1955; (5 folders) (Box 602)
  - Winona Village Housing, 1948-1953; (6 folders) (Box 602)
  - Wins, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 602)
  - Wir, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 602)
  - Wis, 1937-1955; (10 folders) (Box 602)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1937-1962; (28 folders) (Box 602)
  - Wisconsin Bankers Association, 1938-1939 (Box 602)
  - Wit, 1937-1945; (8 folders) (Box 602)
  - Wit, 1945-1962; (17 folders) (Box 603)
  - Witham, Henry B., 1944-1947; (2 folders) (Box 603)
  - WLW Essay Contest If I Were President, (Willkie, Wendell), 1952-1953 (Box 603)
  - Wo, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 603)
  - Wol, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 603)
  - Wolf, 1941-1949; (8 folders) (Box 603)
  - Wolf, 1949-1962; (13 folders) (Box 604)
  - Wolf, Estella, 1937-1938 (Box 604)
  - Wolfe, 1937-1952; (5 folders) (Box 604)
  - Women Colleges, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 604)
  - Women, Dean of (Box 604)
    - Annual report (Box 604)
      - 1937-1938 (Box 604)
      - 1938-1939 (Box 604)
      - 1939-1940 (Box 604)
      - 1942-1943 (Box 604)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 604)
    - Five-Year Report, 1938-1942 (Box 604)
    - Two-Year Report, 1942-1944 (Box 604)
  - Women's Dormitories, 1939-1940 (Box 604)
  - Women's Education (Box 604)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 604)
      Includes "College Women and the War: Proceedings of the Conference held at Northwestern University, November 13-14, 1942"
    - 1943-1944 (Box 604)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 604)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 604)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 604)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 604)
    - [Eddie] Edwards Digest of Articles, 1940-1941 (Box 604)
    - "The American Woman and Her Responsibilities" - Forum at Stephens College, November 6-8, 1941 (Box 604)
  - Women's Residence Halls - Annual reports (Box 604)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 604)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 604)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 604)
  - Women's R.O.T.C. Training, 1942-1943 (Box 604)
  - Woo, 1937-1952; (15 folders) (Box 604)
  - Woo, 1952-1962; (10 folders) (Box 605)
  - Wood, 1953-1954 (Box 605)
  - Wood, Ned, 1938-1939 (Box 605)
  - Woodbridge, Lydia D., 1938-1946 (Box 605)
  - Woodburn House (Box 605)
  - Woodburn, J.A., Dr., 1937-1941; (5 folders) (Box 605)
  - Woodburn Dinner, 1940-1941 (Box 605)
  - Woodburn, James Albert, Dr., 1941-1944; (3 folders) (Box 605)
  - Woods, C.E., Colonel, 1937-1938 (Box 605)
  - Woods, Florence E., 1938-1939 (Box 605)
  - Woods, Robert A., 1940-1945; (3 folders) (Box 605)
  - Wool, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 605)
  - Woollen, Evans (Box 605)
  - Wor, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 605)
  - Work, 1937-1938 (Box 605)
  - Workers Education, 1945-1946 (Box 605)
  - Workers Conference, 1944-1945 (Box 605)
  - Works Progress Administration, 1937-1944; (16 folders) (Box 605)
  - W.P.A., 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 606)
  - Workshop in Intergroup Relations, 1955-1956 (Box 606)
  - World Congress on Education, 1939-1940 (Box 606)
  - World Refugee Year, 1960-1962; (3 folders) (Box 606)
  - World War Scholarships, 1940-1942; (3 folders) (Box 606)
  - Wr, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 606)
  - Wright, Joseph A. (Box 606)
  - Wright, W.W., 1942-1962; (21 folders) (Box 606)
  - Wright-Patterson AFB, 1961-1962 (Box 606)
  - Writers Conference, 1940-1946; (5 folders) (Box 606)
  - Writers Conference, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 607)
  - Wu, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 607)
  - Wy, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 607)
  - Wylie, T.A., 1955-1956 (Box 607)
  - Wylie Hall, 1941-1942 (Box 607)
  - Wylie House (Box 607)
  - X-Y, 1937-1952; (15 folders) (Box 607)
  - X-Y, 1952-1962; (10 folders) (Box 608)
  - Yale University, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 608)
  - Yeager, Edgar L., 1937-1949; (12 folders) (Box 608)
  - Yellen, Samuel (Box 608)
    - 1937-1962 (Box 608)
    - re: literary quarterly, 1943-1946 (Box 608)
  - Yo, 1937-1951; (13 folders) (Box 608)
  - Yo, 1951-1962; (11 folders) (Box 609)
  - You, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 609)
  - Young, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 609)
  - Young, Bert E., 1937-1950; (13 folders) (Box 609)
  - Young Socialist Alliance, 1962 (Box 609)
  - Young, Theodore ("Ted"), 1949-1961 (Box 609)
    (Eggins & Higgins)
  - Y.W.C.A. (Box 609)
    - General (Box 609)
      - 1937-1940 (Box 609)
      - 1941-1947 (Box 609)
      - 1947-1953 (Box 609)
      - 1953-1960 (Box 609)
    - Annual Report (Box 609)
      - 1937-1938 (Box 609)
      - 1938-1939 (Box 609)
      - 1939-1940 (Box 609)
      - 1940-1941 (Box 609)
      - 1941-1942 (Box 609)
      - 1942-1943 (Box 609)
      - 1943-1944 (Box 609)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 609)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 609)
      - 1947-1948 (Box 609)
  - Youth's Digest Scholarship, 1938-1939 (Box 609)
  - Z, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 609)
  - Z, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 610)
  - Ze, 1952-1955; (3 folders) (Box 610)
  - Zi, 1937-1960; (23 folders) (Box 610)
  - Zi, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 611)
  - Zim, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 611)
  - Zoology (Box 611)
  - Department of Zoology, 1938-1939 (Box 611)
    - Applications (Box 611)
  - Zucker, Prof. A.E., 1937-1938 (Box 611)